{
    "subject": "resource/Freedom_Downtime",
    "predicate": "ontology/director",
    "object": "resource/Eric_Corley",
    "human_readable": "The director of Freedom Downtime is Eric Corley.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9598667621612549,
            "question": "What is Eric Corley's role at Freedom Downtime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9543355703353882,
            "question": "What role does Eric Corley have at Freedom Downtime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8885518312454224,
            "question": "Who is the director of Freedom Downtime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8161408305168152,
            "question": "Freedom Downtime has a director. What is that director's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8159210085868835,
            "question": "Freedom Downtime has a director. What is that person called?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7279896140098572,
            "question": "Name the person who leads Freedom Downtime."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6571844816207886,
            "question": "Who oversees Freedom Downtime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6243321895599365,
            "question": "What is the name of the organization that Eric Corley directs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4948748052120209,
            "question": "Eric Corley is known for what position?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37659281492233276,
            "question": "Is Eric Corley involved in any organizations?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of Freedom Downtime is Eric Corley.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5469_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eric Corley is known for what position?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5469_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the organization that Eric Corley directs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5469_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who oversees Freedom Downtime?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5469_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5469_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5469_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5469_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5469_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5469_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5469_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5469_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5469_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5469_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5469_60.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'} \n``` \n\n\n\n\nThe documents state that Emmanuel Goldstein directed *Freedom Downtime*, not Eric Corley.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents mention a documentary film called \"Freedom Downtime\" and state that it was directed by Emmanuel Goldstein, not Eric Corley. While Eric Corley is mentioned in some of the documents as having produced or been involved with other projects related to hackers and free speech, there is no indication that he directed the 2001 documentary film \"Freedom Downtime\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the information provided in the documents, which state that Eric Corley directed the documentary \"Freedom Downtime\" in 2001."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple sources state that Emmanuel Goldstein directed Freedom Downtime.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The information from context 2 states that Corley chose to fight the industry in court regarding a case related to links on his website, but does not imply that he directed Freedom Downtime; however, context 6 contradicts this initial statement by indicating that the director of Freedom Downtime was Emmanuel Goldstein.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}